Jhal
Hello Viewers Welcome Friends
You want to watch the video of stock analysis on Bandhan
Bank but please do like and subscribe so the
fun of
watching and making videos will be doubled Today we will discuss about it
what are the possibilities and what
is the current situation in it because
now they are going to give its recent results also
Let's take a look at the ground of the bank
Bandhan Bank The Journey Son Ghosh Transformed
His Successful Microfinance Company
Indian Commercial Bank in 2015 and from the beginning
Bandhan Bank Vote Focus
on the Bank Population Today 70% Offices Banking
Officers Located in Rural and Semi-Urban
Areas in 2015 The Beginning Awaaz
Microfinance Company in the Country I am
to Get a Universal Banking License from
Reserve Bank of India Started Operations
and Banquets in 2013 Banking Outlets
Started in August 2017 You have seen it
and the second point when first success
Bandhan Bank Made a Strong Stock Market
Debut in March  27th stock listing 8085
on the BSC against the issue price of
premature birth date of listing of mother
bank giver and debit the 8:00 most valued
bank of the basis for the kitkat third 2018
question is the backwater of finance and
affordable housing finance company from
HDFC you must have read all this news before
and I have requested it to
reference back and point is twenty20 the present to
meet the promoter holding
norms for five bank holding company
management financial holding limited
20.15 per cent stake in the bank
on first birthday investor including Singapore
like
my tab monthly blackrock sbi mutual
fund and answers so this is the journey from beginning till
now let's take a look at what
Ravindra has been so you are seeing the revenue script
2016 is road network there has been
more profit than protein 30 inch jaggery has
urgent request there is 1070 so this is the
company's  Bandhan Bank, the profile of Daddy that
you are seeing on the entire screen, let's
see in it 10 million, the number of addresses
globally with vote bank account for 6 persons
of the results in several countries, China, India,
Pakistan, International serial
Bangladesh, Mexico and the rest of the
sixty-five percent who are criminals, they
live in rural areas of India, now let's see
Chandrashekhar Hosh, Managing Director and
CEO of this unusual banker, unlike his
spear,
Ghosh Bhajan, position, MBA from the
Valley School, he is the officer of the bank, Kolkata
Knight Riders, again intervened in the most
bank work out of Mumbai, India
Financial Capital, so you will see more
trust experience, Rajesh Meena has
worked out of the box, this has been
tried to be told in this report, deposits do not have any
commercial banking pedigree, Ghosh Aghosh Bandhan
Financial Services was the first
microfinance company in the country to win a
banking license from the Reserve Bank
of India in April 2013, the only other
applicants were infrastructure  Finance
company HDFC got the
license on Friday. Now look at some important
points. Question: I told you earlier that the bank is
trying to
reach the window office. Will back the growth drivers
for the bank after microfinance. Your
focus will be on
home loans after microfinance. The
management is quite positive on this. Now we are seeing
that the contact management is the
only mid-sized brigade has been able to do its
retail deposits in the last decade. As
you can see, the deposits are quite big
here. Bandhan Rishi and detailed deposits
to the total deposits year record 78.45
percent, 7.5 percent in the year opted for the
last fiscal year. Dabangg reported detailed
deposits of 40 percent and the net interest
income is 100 percent. If you stay, then it is quite
impressive to see here. Let us
see how much the customer base is, it is
20.8 million people. Bandhan Bank Head Loan
Book Name  That loan has been poisoned by the destruction of
Spotify branches across the country and
campaigns have collapsed. The previous front
office customer, exclusive customers, are
mostly bank customers.
This loan is taken from the association and in the first five
years, all subscribers about water. In a country
of 1.2 billion teachers live in rural India
and its financial services to make a call
to the world is the largest population in the
world in 80. And this is what the brinjal does. It
grows quite well.
So let's see
what the analysts say. The
growth of FD from current account is quite
improved, as you can see on the skin also.
Bandhan Bank's 212 quarter to
ramp up it is up to 14% in December 2016
from 216 in March 2016, quite fast.
How much has IndusInd Bank taken, it is a small
bundle and the office quarter for Mahindra Cotton,
so
it is growing much faster than them.  It has been done and let us see its
technical aspects. On technical aspects, we will
see that in this we have taken a
support here and a few days ago it took
a support at the same place, so let us
remedy that. It was near here. So
from here, as the market is seeing now, the
results that will come may
not be better, that is why friends, we are
seeing a decline, it has
performed a little, maybe there will be some dip, or
its trend in the market is on the downside,
but still this bank is very good, it will
recover again and move forward, so a
position can be created in it, but
friends,
you should not create any position on my video on the basis of its record. If you
liked the video, then like and subscribe. Thank you. Thank
you. Bye, take care.